let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "In what is the Colombia Very well program based?",
  answer: "It is based on the improvement of English at the national level of basic upper middle and working",
  options: [
    "It is based on the improvement of English at the national level of basic upper middle and working",
    "It is based on teachers having a good personal level of language",
    "Students can only write in English    ",
    "All of the above"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "According to the first initiative, depending on the results obtained from the diagnostic test, the teacher can access courses:",
  answer: "All of the above",
  options: [
    "of 200 to 500 hours of English lessons.",
    "To immersion programs in English",
    "To training programs in methodology to transform their pedagogical practice.",
    "All of the above"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "How many key initiatives are proposed to ensure a solid foundation for all children in Colombia?",
  answer: "13",
  options: [
    "12",
    "13",
    "5",
    "8"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: "What are the six basic components of the programmes for quality education?",
  answer: "all of the above",
  options: [
    "Teacher support and training - Complete pedagogical model",
    "Support infrastructure and technology - Performance culture",
    "Incorporating the English language outside school-Integration and synergy",
    "all of the above"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "What proposes the fifth accelerated intervention?",
  answer: "Summer camps, extended days, remedial support, extracurricular activities in English ",
  options: [
    "Strengthen digital teaching skills -  Enable remote teacher strategy - Enable co-teaching strategy with foreign volunteers and/or teachers",
    "Hourly intensity of English as a subject for primary school- Extend hourly intensity in secondary and middle school - Support Secretariats considering making official bilingual schools to identify minimum conditions for success",
    "Performance culture- Conduct oral proficiency assessments to students-  Familiarisation and motivation to English (e.g. Bilingual and Official Private Integration)",
    "Summer camps, extended days, remedial support, extracurricular activities in English "
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: "What does the sixth initiative suggest?",
  answer: "Considers integration and synergy between sectors",
  options: [
    "integration",
    "Synergy between sectors",
    "Develop alliances with territorial entities",
    "Considers integration and synergy between sectors"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "What do the accelerated initiatives are for?",
  answer: "achieving faster results",
  options: [
    "longer results and learning",
    "implementing educational resources faster",
    "achieving faster results",
    "none of the above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "What are the alliances with different means of communication with a high potential impact to strengthen the exposure to English?",
  answer: "all of the above",
  options: [
    "National and Regional",
    "audiovisual",
    "radial and written",
    "all of the above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "How will the aids be implemented in the acceleration projects?",
  answer: "with a thematic and regional coordination team",
  options: [
    "with resources from the government",
    "with a thematic and regional coordination team",
    "finding a teacher-only implementation",
    "none of the above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "What are some of the alternative strategies for the gap closure?",
  answer: "All of the above",
  options: [
    "Availability of extra hours for English teachers",
    "Presence of quality English Bachelor programs - Practitioners in the classroom",
    "Good infrastructure and connectivity - Remote teachers",
    "All of the above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 11,
  question: "In the creation of a virtuous circle, which motivates and supports the formation of English, the characterization of English requirements requires:",
  answer: "incorporate the requirements of English into the development of the Common Qualifications Framework",
  options: [
    "To encourage and create the need for training in English ",
    "incorporate the requirements of English into the development of the Common Qualifications Framework",
    "facilitate access to resources",
    "none of the above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 12,
  question: "What is the objective of the Complete Pedagogical Model in an innovative education?",
  answer: "Extend hourly intensity in secondary and middle",
  options: [
    "Extend hourly intensity in secondary and middle",
    "Extracurricular activities in English",
    "Enable remote teacher strategy",
    "English laboratories for immersion with technology support "
  ]
},
{
  numb: 13,
  question: "What are some of the awards and incentives for those who commit to dedicate 200 hours a year to training in English",
  answer: "all of the above",
  options: [
    "Possibility to apply to outdoor immersion (e.g.: USA)",
    "Possibility to apply for education abroad",
    "Possibility of transition to Tutor ",
    "all of the above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 14,
  question: "Capacity building strategies.  (Which of the following in correct)",
  answer: "D is incorrect",
  options: [
    "(A) Talleres en grupo de formación en metodología  (B) Soporte metodológico vía web  (C) Comunidades de docentes (D)   Talleres de refuerzo estudiantil  (E) Tutoring in the classroom ",
    "A and B are correct",
    "C and D are correct",
    "D is incorrect"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 15,
  question: "English, please! is a high quality series developed for grades ________ through which teachers can transform the teaching and learning processes of English as a foreign language and ensure better results.",
  answer: "A and C are correct",
  options: [
    "9 and 10",
    "10 and 11",
    "11",
    "A and C are correct"
  ]
},
];
